pledgingforchange.com 2011-05-30

# Pledging for Change Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy | [Comments Policy](http://pledgingforchange.com/about/privacy#comments) | [Email and Anti Spam Policy](http://pledgingforchange.com/about/privacy#email) | [Business and Earnings Disclaimer](http://pledgingforchange.com/about/privacy#disclaimer)

### Privacy Policy

Pledging for Change takes your privacy very seriously.

Information Collection and Used

You are not required to register on the website (“the website” = http://pledgingforchange.com) or to provide us with any personal information in order to read or benefit from the freely available content supplied on “the website”.

**We may collect the following types of information:**

  * Membership or personal information you provide such as your name or email address within a sign up or subscription form. Your personal information is never shared with others.
  * Cookies : When you visit “the website”, we may send one or more cookies to your computer. A cookie is a small script file containing a string of characters. Cookies are usually used to help us manage our members login access within “the website”.
  * Server Logs : When you access “the website”, our servers automatically record browser information, which is normal for all websites you may visit on the internet. Server logs may include information such as your IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request.
  * Email / Comments : When you send email or add comments to “the website”, these communications may be kept on record in order to reply to you or process your inquiry.
  * Links : Our external links to third party products or services are usually in a format that enables us to track whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our content.
  * External websites : We have no control over the content of external websites that we may link to. External websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect or request personal information from you. _Please read their individual privacy policies._

#### Email and Anti Spam

We never send unsolicited email. Therefore, you will not receive unsolicited communications from “the website”, administrators or agents.

Where you have submitted your request to receive communications, products or services, you will receive the information you requested. In each communication, you are provided with a link to enable you to unsubscribe should you decide that you no longer wish to receive communications from “the website”.

Likewise, we expect you to respect our rights in relation to unsolicited communications and spam.

Please note, all unsolicited post/mail is discarded unopened.

Should you have any concerns or queries in respect of our privacy policy please do not hesitate to [contact us via our contact form](http://www.pledgingforchange.com/about/contact "Pledging for Change contact form").

#### Comments Policy

We look forward to receiving your contributions and personal views in the comments section shown on any of our open articles and encourage you to write your honest opinions.

**Please note however** , that we take an anti spam approach to comments submitted. **All comments are moderated** and will only be published if you have given your name, have not used keywords in your ‘name field’ and have input a **maximum** of one link. We **delete** all comments that are abusive, off-topic, use excessive foul language, are discriminatory or include personal attacks on individuals.

We reserve the right at all times to remove inappropriate links or delete comments which in our opinion are not suitable for publication.

#### Business and Earnings Disclaimer

As with all business matters, please ensure that you **undertake your own due diligence** prior to purchasing any business service or product, that is featured, referred to or linked to on this website, and if necessary ensure that you consult with your professionally qualified legal or accounting advisers.

Pledging for Change does not offer legal or accounting advice. We are not lawyers or accountants.

Some, although not all, of the products and services we feature, make reference to, or link to, may result in us receiving payment in the form of ethical advertising and promotions investment.

These funds do help us with the running costs of the site, our tree planting and grants intiatives and our revenue share program and we **Thank You** in advance for your support in choosing to employ or purchase our ethical businesses products goods or services.  
(Any affiliated income ie Amazon book sales will be dedicated to our new social enterprise Land Ahoy)

Thank you
